PAVEL TURYANSKIY

PHONE: +7 999 239 8819 EMAIL: p.turyanskiy@pm.me

GITHUB: cmcmA20

SUMMARY

I'm a software developer based in Russia. First time I got interested in functional programming in 2014 but my skills were definitely lacking. After studying a bit of hard mathematics and graduating I find myself capable of trying it in a real environment.

I used to do different jobs until I felt comfortable with my general IT experience.

SKILLS AND ACCOMPLISHMENTS

NATURAL LANGUAGES: Russian, English

Programming Languages: C, Haskell, Idris, Octave, Python, x86 asm, Java

(in order of decreasing proficiency)

Translations: Category Theory for Programmers by Bartosz Milewski, see Russian

subtitles

Functional programming: studied Haskell under Artyom "neongreen" Kazak

have done Software Foundations in Idris

NETWORKING: designed and overseen the construction of enterprise ethernet net-

works (up to a hundred of PCs, mainly copper and a bit of fiber) designed and overseen the construction of enterprise virtualization

cluster networks

designed and developed a simple scalable VoIP system for enterprise

using Asterisk + LUA

VIRTUALIZATION: designed, built and maintained virtualization clusters using VMware

ESXi and Proxmox

transitioned legacy infrastructures to private cloud

OS: operated Windows Server (2008 - 2012R2), FreeBSD, Linux (Debian,

CentOS) in production

personally prefer Void Linux and OpenBSD

SECURITY: have basic experience with SIGINT

can do something resembling really secure boot with coreboot +

HEADS and TPM

INTERESTS

MATHEMATICS: casually read nLab, sometimes even understand

skimmed through HoTT book and preparing to study HoTT in Agda studied topology and differential geometry under Iskander Taimanov

completed Robert Ghrist's Calculus: Single Variable

HARDWARE: recently got interested in Thinkpad tinkering

want to learn building UAVs

Work experience

Oct 2017–Jul 2019 (1 year, 10 months)

Information Security Engineer at FSUE NPP Gamma, Russia

was on duty in Samara Arena during FIFA 2018 world cup as a technical security consultant

had done some PowerShell automation, physical fleet configuration management (w/Saltstack)

Pavel Turyanskiy Page 1 of 2 October 29, 2019

operated Rohde&Schwarz and Agilent spectrum analyzers through Python + NIVISA

designed computer networks

had to work with obscure equipment and software

JAN 2017-Aug 2017 (8 months)

Network Engineer at Sibirskie Seti Ltd., Russia

configured equipment of the following vendors: Extreme Networks, Juniper, Cisco, D-Link, TP-Link

wrote network monitoring scripts for Nagios using bash/Python performed equipment and network testing with Python + scapy communicated with NOCs of other ISPs

got an L2 loop in the management network once

SEP 2016–DEC 2016 (4 months)

Engineering Technician at ITVaksa Ltd., Russia

everything from physical cabling to small business network/system design

EDUCATION

SEP 2014–MAY 2018 (4 years)

BS in Informatics at SibSUTI, Novosibirsk, Russia